<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on Sylantiev</title>
    <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on Sylantiev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sylantiev.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Allset</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/allset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/allset/</guid>
      <description>Food Ordering Marketplace for fast &amp;amp; easy pickup, discovery of local eats &amp;amp; coffee shops, and saving money with no high fees.
A user-friendly interface terminal designed for restaurants to easily accept and manage incoming orders has been created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCRN</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/scrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/scrn/</guid>
      <description>SCRN is an application that allows you to save notes from screenshots and read them later.
With SCRN, you can capture screenshots of important information and add notes to them, such as a to-do list or meeting notes. The app also allows you to follow links that may be present in the screenshot, making it easy to access related content or websites.
Additionally, SCRN&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly interface allows you to organize and search through your notes, making it easy to find the information you need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Parking</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/mobile-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/mobile-parking/</guid>
      <description>This app allows users to easily find nearby parking lots and view information such as available spaces, rates, and hours of operation. Users can also use the app to pay for their parking directly, eliminating the need for physical payment methods.
The app&amp;rsquo;s map feature provides a convenient way for users to navigate to their desired parking lot, making parking hassle-free. This app is perfect for anyone who frequently drives and needs to find parking quickly and easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Okean Elzy</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/okean-elzy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/okean-elzy/</guid>
      <description>Design of the official website for the Ukrainian rock band, Okean Elzy. I was able to capture the band&amp;rsquo;s unique style and energy, creating a website that truly reflects their music and image.
I used modern design elements and intuitive navigation to make the site easy to use for both fans and the band. Visitors can easily access information about upcoming concerts, purchase merchandise, and connect with the band on social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trill</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/trill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/trill/</guid>
      <description>Trill is a platform designed for efficient time management in the workplace. It allows users to accurately track their work time and create detailed reports of their activity. Additionally, Trill provides tools for project estimates, giving users the ability to better plan and budget their work. Users can also create custom reports to fit their specific needs. Trill is a powerful tool that can help increase productivity and streamline workflows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bwin</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/bwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/bwin/</guid>
      <description>Redesign of the web and mobile platform is a project that focuses on improving the user experience and visual design of the website and mobile application.
The redesign includes a new visual design with a clean and modern look and feel, new iconography that makes the navigation more intuitive, animations that enhance the overall user experience and make the platform more engaging.
The goal of this redesign is to make the Bwin platform more user-friendly, visually appealing and easy to navigate for the users, in order to increase engagement and satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wambrella</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/wambrella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/wambrella/</guid>
      <description>Wambrella is a platform that allows users to manage their weather experience by defining their personal comfort level based on current weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loupe</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/loupe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/loupe/</guid>
      <description>Loupe is an app that allows users to easily search for and book appointments with local beauticians. Users can browse through a directory of beauticians, view their profiles and ratings, and make a booking at their convenience.
The app also allows users to filter their search by location, services offered, and availability, making it easy to find the perfect beautician for their needs. Additionally, users can receive reminders for upcoming appointments and can cancel or reschedule if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settle</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/settle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/settle/</guid>
      <description>Settle is an app and web-site that allows users to pre-order food and dine at restaurants without waiting. My role in the project was to work on the user experience (UX) design, visual design and logo design. I designed the user interface and user flow, making sure that the app is intuitive and easy to use. I also created a visually appealing and consistent design using modern design elements, typography and color schemes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watsons</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/watsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/watsons/</guid>
      <description>The Watsons shop web-site is an e-commerce platform for Watsons, a leading health and beauty retail chain. The site allows customers to browse and purchase a wide range of health, beauty, and personal care products from Watsons, including skincare, makeup, vitamins, and more.
The site features a user-friendly interface, easy navigation, and a variety of tools to help customers find the products they need, such as product filters, search bar and product recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Coffee Machine</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/hello-coffee-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/hello-coffee-machine/</guid>
      <description> The project at Aimbulance aimed to streamline morning routines by combining the coffee consumption and check-in processes. A phygital coffee machine was developed, which allowed employees to order their coffee and automatically check in via their mobile phones. By visiting the coffee machine&amp;rsquo;s page, employees could easily start their day with a hot cup of coffee and a hassle-free check-in experience.
Awards Ukrainian Design The Very Best Of 2014 Kakadu Silver 2014 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OftenType</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/oftentype/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/oftentype/</guid>
      <description>The project introduces an innovative mobile app that provides a &amp;ldquo;quick keys&amp;rdquo; feature, offering users pre-made information templates that effortlessly integrate with their messaging keyboard. This solution simplifies and streamlines communication by allowing users to access and share relevant information through a seamless user interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlemagne the Myth</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/charlemagne-the-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/charlemagne-the-myth/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Stars of Now</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/work/pepsi-stars-of-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/work/pepsi-stars-of-now/</guid>
      <description>The Pepsi Stars of Now project aimed to support young musicians in their pursuit of fame and recognition. A platform was developed to enable aspiring bands to showcase their talent by creating personalized pages and uploading up to three tracks. This initiative provided emerging artists with an opportunity to gain exposure and connect with their first fans. The winning band was awarded a professionally produced music video and airplay on Europa Plus Ukraine radio, offering a significant boost to their budding career.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
