<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archive on Sylantiev</title>
    <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archive on Sylantiev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sylantiev.com/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Black Ops TV Show</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/black-ops-tv-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/black-ops-tv-show/</guid>
      <description>In order to promote exclusive content on channels such as Viasat Explorer, Viasat History, Viasat Nature, and Viasat TV1000, monthly promotional pages are created. These pages feature unique designs and structures based on the specific themes of the showcased programs.
A recent example includes the promotional page for Viasat Explorer&amp;rsquo;s documentary series &amp;ldquo;Black Ops,&amp;rdquo; which focuses on global intelligence agencies&amp;rsquo; operations. The design and structure of the promotional page were tailored to reflect the series&amp;rsquo; theme and content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MasterCard PayPass</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mastercard-paypass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mastercard-paypass/</guid>
      <description>This project focused on promoting the advantages of MasterCard® PayPass™ and contactless payment technology. The created website featured various sections that provided valuable information on utilizing the card and highlighted locations where the new payment method could be employed. The project aimed to educate users on the convenience and efficiency offered by contactless payment solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viasat World</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/viasat-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/viasat-world/</guid>
      <description>The project involved creating monthly promo pages to highlight exclusive shows on Viasat Explorer, Viasat History, Viasat Nature, and Viasat TV1000 channels. Each promo page featured unique designs and structures, tailored to the specific themes of the featured TV programs. The team successfully designed 25 websites for Viasat Broadcasting satellite channels and adapted their content to cater to audiences in seven countries: Czech Republic, Serbia, Poland, Croatia, Hungary, Romania, and Bulgaria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Moments</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/pepsi-moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/pepsi-moments/</guid>
      <description>The Pepsi Moments project focused on enhancing the experiences of today&amp;rsquo;s youth by providing a platform for sharing and gaining social approval. Inspired by the global idea &amp;ldquo;PEPSI. LIVE FOR NOW&amp;rdquo; the platform allowed users to capture photos, apply filters and collages, and share their moments with the community. Integrated with VKontakte and Facebook, the platform offered a seamless user experience without requiring additional registration.
The platform featured multiple sections, including Share, Catch, Support, Explore, and Fill up, offering users various ways to engage with their moments, receive stylish lifestyle gifts, and gather inspiration from others around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice Wallet</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/advice-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/advice-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Advice Wallet - social networking platform for referral marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iBox</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/ibox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/ibox/</guid>
      <description>New interface terminals IBox. Terminal iBox can be funded mobile phones, recharge purses WebMoney, repay loans and make bank transactions.
Icon sets
Keyboard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Retro</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/pepsi-retro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/pepsi-retro/</guid>
      <description>The Pepsi Retro project provided online support for a campaign celebrating Pepsi&amp;rsquo;s anniversary in Ukraine and the introduction of Pepsi Retro. The goal was to engage modern teenagers with the culture of the 1980s and evoke nostalgia in older audiences through the Pepsi-Cola Time Machine.
The campaign leveraged the previously implemented Pepsi Likerzzz platform, which already had 140,396 users. The platform was redesigned, and user profiles were analyzed to switch their modern interests and music preferences to those of the 80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1576</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/1576/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/1576/</guid>
      <description>The first structured public library Ukrainian world, the reader and the compiler which can be any! 1576.ua allow everyone interested to hear, listen and see characters Ukrainian classics, to feel the depth of personalities, most of which are known to us only by the so-called &amp;ldquo;summit achievements.&amp;rdquo; We want to restore the rich and ambiguous world of Ukrainian culture in the diversity of languages, sounds and colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mabila</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mabila/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mabila/</guid>
      <description>Mabila - web-site about gadgets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KRM</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/krm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/krm/</guid>
      <description>The KRM tour operator website showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s specialization in outdoor activities and extreme tourism in Crimea. By bringing together expert instructors, guides, and athletes, KRM aims to provide visitors with unique, off-the-beaten-path experiences beyond the typical beach vacation.
The website presents a variety of excursion programs catered to both professional travelers and beginners, offering activities such as trekking, canyoning, rock climbing, mountaineering, zip-lining, abseiling, diving, cave exploration, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seat Leon &amp; Ibiza</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/seat-leon-ibiza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/seat-leon-ibiza/</guid>
      <description>The project involved creating a website to showcase Seat Leon and Seat Ibiza automobiles in an engaging and interactive manner. Visitors to the site were guided through a narrative that highlighted the cars&amp;rsquo; design, technical features, and financial services. The story-driven presentation allowed users to explore the key aspects of the vehicles, culminating in the opportunity to sign up for a test drive. This immersive approach provided a unique and memorable experience while effectively promoting the Seat Leon and Seat Ibiza models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cesu 23</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/cesu-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/cesu-23/</guid>
      <description>Concept design for Cesu23</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citroen DS4</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/citroen-ds4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/citroen-ds4/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;No-manifesto&amp;rdquo; campaign, in collaboration with Citroën DS4, aimed to provide an outlet for individuals with active lifestyles to express their opposition to various frustrations. The idea centered around creating personalized protest manifestos on the campaign&amp;rsquo;s promotional website.
Upon logging in with Facebook, users could say &amp;ldquo;No!&amp;rdquo; to various annoyances, such as the pursuit of fashion or impractical household items. Each &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo; led to the destruction of an object symbolizing the source of frustration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TUI</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/tui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/tui/</guid>
      <description>The TUI Travel Operator project involved designing a user-friendly website for the renowned travel company, TUI. The primary focus of the site was to streamline the travel booking process by offering a seamless interface for tour selection and booking. By showcasing various travel options on the main page and providing an intuitive user experience, the website aimed to make it easy for customers to explore and book their ideal tours, ensuring a positive experience with the TUI brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathtick</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mathtick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mathtick/</guid>
      <description>Mathtick is a math-based game designed to resemble a magnetic board, with a chalk-like font to enhance its visual appeal. The application incorporates magnetized badges representing numbers, which can be moved around the board in a logical manner. This engaging and interactive game offers a creative way to encourage learning and enjoyment of mathematics while simulating the experience of using a traditional magnetic board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>«Evropa» center</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/evropa-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/evropa-center/</guid>
      <description>Commercial and business center «Evropa». Design of the web-site for Ekaterinburg&amp;rsquo;s commercial and business centre «Evropa».</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shake</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/shake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/shake/</guid>
      <description>Shake Cocktails web-site. Shake is a stylish youth brand. It was created specially for those who can enjoy their life and likes to emphasize their individuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lavkarboklubben</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/lavkarboklubben/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/lavkarboklubben/</guid>
      <description>Lavkarboklubben is a club for low-carb diet enthusiasts. As art director and visual designer, I created a cohesive visual identity through the logo, iconography and visual elements for website. Aiming to create an easy-to-use, visually pleasing platform to help members achieve their diet goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TUI Egypt</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/tui-egypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/tui-egypt/</guid>
      <description>European class of vacation in Egypt from TUI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepsi Likerzzz</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/pepsi-likerzzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/pepsi-likerzzz/</guid>
      <description>Pepsi Likerzzz is a community designed for young people with diverse interests, providing a platform to make connections, express themselves, and gain recognition for who they are. Aligned with the &amp;ldquo;I live for now&amp;rdquo; motto, this platform encourages self-expression and engagement among its users.
The core concept of Pepsi Likerzzz is enabling users to receive attention and acknowledgement by simply showcasing their interests through &amp;ldquo;likes&amp;rdquo; in various categories, such as events, music, and activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slavutich</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/slavutich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/slavutich/</guid>
      <description>Promo site for Slavutich beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EnMark</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/enmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/enmark/</guid>
      <description>EnMark - web-site and icons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConteinerX</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/conteinerx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/conteinerx/</guid>
      <description>Icons for categories of site ConteinerX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia Trend Labs</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/nokia-trend-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/nokia-trend-labs/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Park Drive</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/park-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/park-drive/</guid>
      <description>Park Drive - first Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;electronic showroom&amp;rdquo;, where you can pick out any car anywhere in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia Ovi</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/nokia-ovi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/nokia-ovi/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacobs</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/jacobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/jacobs/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTS DJ Parade</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mts-dj-parade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/mts-dj-parade/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeans Site</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/jeans-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/jeans-site/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodwine</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/goodwine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/goodwine/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HCM</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/hcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/hcm/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muzon</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/muzon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/muzon/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solomenka</title>
      <link>https://sylantiev.com/archive/solomenka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylantiev.com/archive/solomenka/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
